We're back pitches
Pitch Perfect 2 is a comedy, music film directed by Elizabeth Banks.
The Bellas are back, and they are better than ever.
After being humiliated in front of none other than the President of the United
States of America, the Bellas are taken out of the Aca-Circuit.
In order to clear their name, and regain their status, the Bellas take on a seemingly
impossible task: winning an international competition no American team has ever won.
In order to accomplish this monumental task, they need to strengthen the bonds of friendship
and sisterhood and blow away the competition with their amazing aca-magic!
With all new friends and old rivals tagging along for the trip,
the Bellas can hopefully accomplish their dreams.
Beca Mitchell, played by Anna Kendrick.
Chloe Beale, played by Brittany Snow.
Emily Junk, played by Hailee Steinfeld.
Fat Amy, played by Rebel Wilson.
Cynthia Rose, played by Ester Dean.
Bumper Allen, played by Adam Devine.
Pitch Perfect 2 is a 2015 American musical comedy film directed and
produced by Elizabeth Banks and written by Kay Cannon.
It is a sequel to the 2012 film Pitch Perfect, and
it is Banks' directorial debut.
The film follows the Barden University Bellas, an all-female a cappella group, who
face off against a German group in a world a capella championship.
The film's emsemble cast features Anna Kendrick, Rebel Wilson, Brittany Snow, Skylar Astin, Adam DeVine, Anna Camp, Ben Platt, Hana Mae Lee, Alexis Knapp, Ester Dean, Kelly Jakle, Shelley
Regner, John Michael Higgins and Elizabeth Banks—all reprising their roles from the previous film—as well as Hailee Steinfeld, Katey Sagal, Birgitte Hjort Sørensen, and Flula Borg.
Pitch Perfect 2 was released in the United States on
May 15, 2015, by Universal Pictures.
It grossed $287.5 million worldwide, surpassing the total gross of
the original film ($115.4 million) in five days.
It became the highest-grossing musical comedy film of all
time, overtaking School of Rock ($131.3 million).
A sequel, Pitch Perfect 3, was released on December 22, 2017.
The film explores themes of sequel, singer, audition,
group of friends, duringcreditsstinger.
The tone is lighthearted and uplifting.